[{"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130703pmt", "aSentId": 4, "question": "And that's all someone would need to do to fire a shot, if it was fully loaded?", "qSentId": 3}, {"answer": "I just got a partial DNA profile and that matched Trayvon Martin.", "docId": "130703pmt", "aSentId": 9, "question": "Do you know whose blood that was?", "qSentId": 8}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130703pmt", "aSentId": 33, "question": "The DNA you developed from the pistol grip of the defendant's gun, it was positive for blood, correct?", "qSentId": 32}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130703pmt", "aSentId": 35, "question": "And then there was a mixture, the major matched the defendant, George Zimmerman?", "qSentId": 34}, {"answer": "Yes, Trayvon Martin was excluded as being a possible contributor to this mixture on the grip.", "docId": "130703pmt", "aSentId": 37, "question": "And you were able to exclude Trayvon Martin as having DNA on the pistol grip, is that correct?", "qSentId": 36}, {"answer": "Yes, well, you know, we should point out, of course, that the jury here, most of them came in with a very limited knowledge of this case.", "docId": "130703pmt", "aSentId": 42, "question": "Where are we left then in terms of George Zimmerman's claim that his life was at risk?", "qSentId": 41}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130703pmt", "aSentId": 55, "question": "They're going into a weekend, 48 hours for that jury to think about it before the defense really get a chance to come back?", "qSentId": 54}, {"answer": "Well, you know, there has to be a voice identification of that screams.", "docId": "130703pmt", "aSentId": 74, "question": "Is that the case?", "qSentId": 73}, {"answer": "I disagree with that.", "docId": "130703pmt", "aSentId": 79, "question": "How do you feel as you approach the end of the prosecution?", "qSentId": 78}, {"answer": "I think it's very significant because we also heard evidence there was no George Zimmerman DNA on Trayvon's hands or under his fingernails or on the cuffs of his sleeve.", "docId": "130703pmt", "aSentId": 84, "question": "How significant was that moment in court do you think today?", "qSentId": 83}, {"answer": "I think there is no merit to that because we've heard all these theories that the star witness of this case would be Jon Good or Rachel Jeantel, when all along George Zimmerman has given at least five statements.", "docId": "130703pmt", "aSentId": 90, "question": "Is there any merit to that argument?", "qSentId": 89}, {"answer": "Well, let me give you the background.", "docId": "130703pmt", "aSentId": 103, "question": "What is the answer to that question, do you think?", "qSentId": 102}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130703pmt", "aSentId": 107, "question": "Do you consider yourself a fair person?", "qSentId": 106}, {"answer": "That would be true.", "docId": "130703pmt", "aSentId": 112, "question": "Would that be true?", "qSentId": 111}, {"answer": "I mean, I wouldn't be, but I understand that having interviewed many, many people that most people are quite nervous.", "docId": "130703pmt", "aSentId": 114, "question": "Well, let me ask you something, while we're talking here, you're a professional but most people who would not be a professional, if I'm asking you questions that are on television, would you think you'd be a little bit nervous?", "qSentId": 113}, {"answer": "Or being overly defensive.", "docId": "130703pmt", "aSentId": 117, "question": "And as quite nervous, do you think people interpret somebody's being nervous as perhaps not being truthful?", "qSentId": 116}, {"answer": "So I would first make sure that every one of the jurors understood that the decision to take the stand is going to be my decision, and the reasons why I wouldn't have somebody take the stand, just being nervous, perhaps that alone would make you think maybe he's not being truthful.", "docId": "130703pmt", "aSentId": 120, "question": "And for that reason, there is nothing to gain by putting Zimmerman on the stand given we already have five different effective statements from him?", "qSentId": 119}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130703pmt", "aSentId": 129, "question": "Is there anything to be gained, Robert, by Zimmerman taking the stand given the amount of material from his own mouth that we've already heard?", "qSentId": 128}, {"answer": "The jury can see him, look him in the eye, and that's the best way to make a determination if you're believing that person was actually in fear for his life.", "docId": "130703pmt", "aSentId": 131, "question": "What is that?", "qSentId": 130}, {"answer": "HAPIRO: You know, it is so hard to evaluate.", "docId": "130703pmt", "aSentId": 136, "question": "Could that be a tipping point for them to say, we've got to have George up there?", "qSentId": 135}, {"answer": "Or of any relative of a victim.", "docId": "130703pmt", "aSentId": 139, "question": "Right, because you can't win a cross-examination of a grieving mother, right?", "qSentId": 138}, {"answer": "I think they have overcharged.", "docId": "130703pmt", "aSentId": 164, "question": "Well, have they overcharged to start with?", "qSentId": 163}, {"answer": "Well, malice is a legal term.", "docId": "130703pmt", "aSentId": 176, "question": "Isn't that intent there to think badly of this person?", "qSentId": 175}, {"answer": "I think it possibly could be interpreted by people as ill will, but it -- again, you have the reasonable doubt standard that you have to get over.", "docId": "130703pmt", "aSentId": 179, "question": "Isn't that ill will?", "qSentId": 178}, {"answer": "I don't know but that's going to be the question.", "docId": "130703pmt", "aSentId": 192, "question": "That is what with racial profiling or just profiling of this is a bad person, he's still coming at him with malicious intent, isn't he?", "qSentId": 191}, {"answer": "That is a key question and that's what the lawyers are going to be arguing in their closing argument and that's what the jury is going to be sitting on and deciding.", "docId": "130703pmt", "aSentId": 194, "question": "Is that a key question?", "qSentId": 193}, {"answer": "I haven't heard him testify directly --", "docId": "130703pmt", "aSentId": 198, "question": "Do you believe him?", "qSentId": 197}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130703pmt", "aSentId": 200, "question": "From what you've seen in the statements and the interviews?", "qSentId": 199}, {"answer": "You know, I don't want to compare anything to the Simpson case and I don't really talk about the Simpson case.", "docId": "130703pmt", "aSentId": 204, "question": "Do you feel that it's as a motive, as, say, the O.J. Simpson case?", "qSentId": 203}, {"answer": "You know, we're going to see the opposite side of that in the Oscar Pistorius case where in South Africa you cannot use deadly force unless deadly force is being used upon you.", "docId": "130703pmt", "aSentId": 212, "question": "Is it just not an excuse for almost every gang banger thug in America to say hey, I was just acting in self-defense?", "qSentId": 211}, {"answer": "I think it can be significant in the sense that it's going to be very emotional testimony.", "docId": "130703pmt", "aSentId": 232, "question": "How significant could that be in tipping the scales back in the favor of the prosecution case?", "qSentId": 231}, {"answer": "If it is enhanced the way I think it will be, they could win the battle and lose the war, absolutely.", "docId": "130703pmt", "aSentId": 264, "question": "So it really is all or nothing for George Zimmerman, isn't it?", "qSentId": 263}, {"answer": "Honestly, Piers, I just don't see any percentage in that.", "docId": "130703pmt", "aSentId": 266, "question": "Would you put him on the stand, particularly if the Trayvon family members' testimony is heart rendering and you sense the jury had been moved by him?", "qSentId": 265}, {"answer": "If I was looking at it from a pure legal standpoint, I would say an acquittal.", "docId": "130703pmt", "aSentId": 290, "question": "What do you think that will be?", "qSentId": 289}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130703pmt", "aSentId": 306, "question": "You don't have to wait until you are almost dead before you can defend yourself?", "qSentId": 305}, {"answer": "Not necessarily in the criminal justice system.", "docId": "130703pmt", "aSentId": 342, "question": "Doesn't there have to be accountability for that?", "qSentId": 341}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "130703pmt", "aSentId": 372, "question": "There has to be some form of justice for Trayvon Martin, doesn't it?", "qSentId": 371}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "130703pmt", "aSentId": 389, "question": "That is a different ball game, just as even in a civil action, right?", "qSentId": 388}, {"answer": "They are very much the strongest institution in the country and they laid down the law 48 hours ago to Mohamed Morsy and the opposition saying, that if you don't get your act together, you're out and we're in, and what happened was last night we heard a speech from Mohamed Morsy who, as he made it clear, that he wasn't going to give in to their ultimatum.", "docId": "130703pmt", "aSentId": 437, "question": "Who is in charge?", "qSentId": 436}, {"answer": "Well, that's a good question.", "docId": "130703pmt", "aSentId": 442, "question": "But where does it leave democracy in Egypt, the democracy that everyone celebrated with the Arab spring now looks to be in taters?", "qSentId": 441}, {"answer": "It's already been pretty bad today across much of the Deep South, Piers.", "docId": "130703pmt", "aSentId": 491, "question": "Samantha, how bad is it going to be?", "qSentId": 490}]